minitek.gr 2014-07-05

# Minitek - Privacy policy

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or when you purchase a subscription. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you are asked to enter your name and email address. When purchasing a product you are asked to enter your first and last name, your address, city, zip or postal code, country, state or province and email. In some payment options you may be asked to enter credit card data. However, this data is handled by [Avangate](http://www.minitek.gr/avangate.com). Avangate provides a secure and reliable platform for selling our software products online. Your private data is 100% safe, as Avangate complies with the latest online security standards.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To process transactions
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested
  * To send periodic newsletters
  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  * Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future newsletters, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each newsletter

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Online Privacy Policy

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our website, you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Minitek.gr is entitled to change or update this Privacy Policy at its own discretion without any obligation of prior notification.

This policy was last modified on 06/14/2013.
